What Is Love
What is love?
Baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more
Baby don't hurt me
Don't hurt me no more
What is love?
Yeah hey
I don't know why you're not there
I give you my love but you don't care
So what is right?
What is wrong?
Gimme a sign
What is love?
Baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more
Oh I don't know what can
I do
What else can
I say?
It's up to you
I know we're one just me and you
I can't go on
What is love?
Baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more
Oh baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more
What is love?
Don't hurt me
I want no other no other lover
This is our life our time
We are together
I need you forever
Is it love?
What is love?
Baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more
Yeah hey
What is love?
Baby don't hurt me don't hurt me no more